officeholidays.com 2018-10-19

# Privacy Policy for OfficeHolidays.com | Office Holidays

#### Privacy Policy for OfficeHolidays.com

### INTRODUCTION

The site editor takes your right to privacy seriously, and wants you to feel comfortable using this web site. This privacy policy deals with personally-identifiable information (referred to as "data" below) that may be collected by this site. This policy does not apply to other entities that are not owned or controlled by the site editor, nor does it apply to persons that are not employees or agents of the site editor, or that are not under the site editor's control.

### 1\. COLLECTION OF DATA

As on many web sites, the site editor may automatically receive general information that is contained in server log files, such as your IP address. The information captured is essential and necessary to ensure the security of the site. The information is never accessed for marketing purposes or shared with any third-party.

We do not ask you for any individual information when you use our site. If you choose to sign up to our weekly update newsletter, we will need your email and consent to send you the weekly newsletter. We do not use that email address for any other purpose than the newsletter. The email addresses are held by [Mailchimp](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).

We also collect anonymised publicly available information from social networking sites such as Facebook and Twitter, for example likes, shares, tweets and posts about Office Holidays. This information is provided to us by a third party and is fully anonymised so we cannot see who has posted the information. This information is used for internal analysis purposes.

#### How we collect personal information 

We only collect your personal information when you provide it to us when you subscribe to a newsletter, submit feedback or send us a communication.

### 2\. USE OF DATA

Data may be used to customize and improve your user experience on this site. Efforts will be made to prevent your data being made available to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) your consent is obtained, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out for the sharing of data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires interaction with a third party, or is provided by a third party, such as an application service provider; (iv) pursuant to legal action or law enforcement; (v) it is found that your use of this site violates the site editor's policy, terms of service, or other usage guidelines, or if it is deemed reasonably necessary by the site editor to protect the site editor's legal rights and/or property; or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party, in which case that third party will be able to use the data in the same manner as set forth in this policy. In the event you choose to use links displayed on this web site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies published on those sites.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. The third-party cookies are necessary to avoid fraud and reporting on the adverts. For users of this site within the EEA, when you first visit this site, we ask you to accept the use of these cookies. You can decline the use of these cookies, but you will still see adverts on this site, but they will be less relevant you, which most users find more annoying than relevant adverts.

The advertising providers may use this anonymous information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

We do not use direct marketing. Any information we receive from you, stays with us. It is not shared with third parties other than the analytics and advertising uses described on this page and the cookie control page. 

### 3\. COOKIES

Like almost any other web site, this web site sets and uses cookies to enhance your user experience -- to remember your personal settings, for instance. Advertisements may display on this web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer; such cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the parties providing the advertisement. However, the parties providing the advertising do not have access to this site's cookies. These parties usually use non-personally-identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to this site. Information about cookies and their use on www.officeholidays.com.

We use analytics services to measure how many people use this website and monitor the overall performance of our website. The analytics service has been configured to anonymise your IP address, so you cannot be identified. The cookies used by the analytics service are necessary to ensure the ongoing operation of the site.

### 4\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Changes may be made to this policy from time to time. You will be notified of substantial changes to this policy either by through the posting of a prominent announcement on the site..

### 5\. NO GUARANTEES

While this privacy policy states standards for maintenance of data, and while efforts will be made to meet the said standards, the site editor is not in a position to guarantee compliance with these standards. There may be factors beyond the site editor's control that may result in disclosure of data. Consquently, the site editor offers no warranties or representations as regards maintenance or non-disclosure of data.

## 6\. Links

This Site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave this Site and to read the privacy statements applicable on those sites. This privacy policy does not apply to information collected on third parties’ sites.

### 7\. CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions about this policy or about this web site, please feel free to contact the site administrator. 

### 8\. Third Party Privacy Policies

  * Cloudflare: 
  * Facebook: <http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info-on-other>
  * Twitter: <https://twitter.com/privacy>
  * YouTube:  <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/faq/#toc-cookies>
  * AddThis: <http://www.addthis.com/privacy>

## Translate this page
